propertyworld.com 2014-04-27

# Privacy Policy - PropertyWorld.com

**  
Privacy Policy**

PropertyWorld is committed to protecting the privacy of our users and contributors. We seek to provide a safe, secure user experience. When you register for property updates, fill out an enquiry form, carry out a property search or register with us to add property or business details to the database the information you supply about yourself is required in order to provide you with the information or service you have requested. Except as provided in this privacy policy, we do not supply your personal information to any other person unless you have expressly authorised us so to do.

When you submit your personal details to us as described below you will be deemed to have consented to their use by us in the ways indicated.

**Registration**

When you register with PropertyWorld either as a user or a contributor the information you provide (i) allows us to send messages to you when managing enquiries online (ii) allows us to contact you with assistance, if necessary; (iii) allows us to verify the legitimacy of your entry or advertisement; (iv) enables us to customise the content of our site to meet your specific needs; and (v) enables us to analyse user trends and make product improvements to the Site and services offered. 

**General Information**

The information with which users or contributors provide us, such as which areas are visited most frequently and which services users or contributors access the most is used in analysing the needs of Site visitors in general. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users or contributors and how we can continue to create a better overall user experience. We may share this information with our partners so that they too may understand how PropertyWorld users and contributors use our site.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Personal Information**

In some instances we may ask for more specific information. This information may include your name, address, telephone number, postcode etc. We may use this information to make you aware of additional products and services that you may find of interest either directly or via third party suppliers, or to contact you regarding site updates and enhancements. We may also ask you for other information such as your interests, your opinions regarding the site, and lifestyle questions in an effort to deliver you the best possible Site experience. 

**Opt Out**

PropertyWorld has been developed so that once you have entered your details you automatically receive subsequent deliveries of information such as notice of site upgrades and enhancements, new property entries or features, user tips, and additional information on products and services. Should you desire to 'opt out' from, or terminate receiving, this information please utilize the 'opt out' or 'unsubscribe' link in the received message or update the appropriate section of your personal folder.

**Surveying Opinion**

PropertyWorld values opinion and comment from users and contributors so we may from time to time conduct online surveys. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Typically the information is aggregated and used to make improvements to PropertyWorld and to develop appealing content, features and promotions for users and contributors. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey.

**Feedback**

Please submit any feedback to PropertyWorld. Any feedback submitted becomes the property of PropertyWorld. We may use this feedback, such as success stories, for marketing purposes or to contact you for further feedback on the site. We will seek your written or email approval should we want to use your personal success story for marketing purposes. Feedback is used primarily for internal purposes to aid us in the improvement of the site.

**Disclosure of Information**

Excepting the aforementioned provisions PropertyWorld will not disclose information about your individual visits to our website or any of the personal information that you provide such as your name, address or telephone number to any outside parties except when we believe the law requires and when such disclosure is necessary in the delivery of information. However, we may record and share aggregated information with our partners. Additionally any information that you enter on a co-branded registration page becomes the property of both PropertyWorld and the co-branded partner. In that instance PropertyWorld is not responsible for any of the information received by our partner company. In some instances personal information may be passed from PropertyWorld to our partners in order to automatically pre-fill fields on their websites. While we make all efforts to protect your privacy when negotiating our partnerships we are not responsible for their use of your personal information. To that end we encourage you to read the privacy statements of our partners or request them directly from our partners in the event they are not readily available. If you remain concerned about information disclosure please contact us via the feedback section on our site or at the address listed below.

**Cookies**

'Cookies' enable small pieces of information to be stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. PropertyWorld uses cookies in several ways. We use cookies to allow you to login, to keep track of your preferences and for us to track usage of the site. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but if you prefer you can edit your browser options to block them in the future, although this may negatively impact on your use of the site.

**Enquiries**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website you can contact us by e-mail via the feedback section on our site, or at the following address:

SICO Technical Services Ltd., t/a  
PropertyWorld.com  
P.O. Box 412  
Surbiton  
Surrey  
KT6 7WZ  
England

Customer Service [enquiries@propertyworld.com](mailto:enquiries@propertyworld.com)

Thank you for using PropertyWorld.com
